http://www.logbooks.com/pages/privacy

Privacy | Log Books Unlimited®: Your Online LogBooks Store. Buy Today!
Hello Logbooks.com Visitor!
Looks like you are in Canada. Please use our Canadian websitewww.logbooks.ca
Welcome to Log Books Unlimited!
Attention! You are browsing from , please proceed to the corresponding page:
Hello Logbooks Unlimited Visitor!
Looks like you are in Canada. Please use our Canadian websitewww.logbooks.ca
www.logbooks.com (USA)
Register
Your cart (0)
Emergency Generator
Engineers (Boilers)
1-877-LOG-BOOK
(564)    (2665)
Security
At Log Books Unlimited, we respect the privacy and security issues of our clients, and employ the world's second largest certificate provider GeoTrust ® for the protection of your personal information against unauthorized access, loss or theft. Transactions on LogBooks.com are secured by 256-bit encryption and a $10,000 warranty. Though we use software that receives and records the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the; we make no attempt to link these addresses with the identity of individuals visiting our site. Personal Information Your information is strictly obtained if you supply it voluntarily. It is disclosed through a Log Books Unlimited office under video surveillance solely to the staff who manage your order, or respond to your requests; except where required by law. Third party involvement for the purposes of shipping view Name, Address and Phone Number only. Under Canada's Privacy Act; you will be informed that your personal information is being collected, the purpose for which it is being collected, and that you have access to it.
Social Media
Logbooks.com is linked to social media groups where we may ask for your name and email, so that we may effectively involve customer service to respond for your comments or inquiries. Any information volunteered through email by our visitors will be held private. The privacy policies of the links themselves are autonomous; Log Books Unlimited is not responsible for any personally identifiable information collected from them.
Cookies
A Cookie is digital information used to enhance the visitor's repeat visit. They do not link to any personally identifiable information.
Ice Rink (Refrigeration)
Engineers (Boilers)
650 Runnymede Rd.
